(Howard:)Unless she's willing to jump off
a moving train...
(Howard:)...tuck and roll down the side of a hill,
she will eventually succumb...
(Howard:)...to the acquired taste
that is Howard Wolowitz.
(Leonard:)My money's on tuck and roll.
(Sheldon:)I'm confused.
(Sheldon:)I thought you were involved in some sort of
socially intimate pairing with Leslie Winkle.
(Howard:)- Let me explain to you how this works.
- All right.
(Sheldon:)- That's Summer Glau.
- Yes?
(Howard:)That's it.
(Raj:)Hang on a sec.
(Raj:)- Why do you get first crack at her?
- Uh, well, let's see. Couple reasons.
(Howard:)One, I saw her first.
(Raj:)No, you didn't. I did.
(Howard:)Fair enough. But then let me move on
to number two.
(Howard:)Unlike you, I can actually talk to women
when I'm sober.
(Raj:)You fail to take into account
that even mute, I am foreign and exotic...
(Raj:)...while you, on the other hand,
are frail and pasty.
(Howard:)Well, you know the old saying.